{
    "id": "8445b406875d437882c2341c1bb3b87a",
    "title": "In Spite Of, Despite, However, Though, Although",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We went out ………………….. the rain.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "despite",
                "in spite of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "2c6b3d982b8f410b833ac7281de85a11"
        },
        {
            "question": "We went out ………………….. it was raining.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "though",
                "however",
                "in spite of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "07cc45c52f8b4d888c3a2848cc9118fe"
        },
        {
            "question": "The judge sent her to prison ……………….. the fact that she had very small children.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "despite",
                "however",
                "though"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e661897495754c88ad39972e5ba63fe0"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… I didn’t enjoy the movie, I watched it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "However"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "15ce6b23853f4ae98979dbd43945d17a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I enjoyed the party ……………….. I didn’t know anybody there.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "though",
                "however",
                "in spite of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "69ccaba92e0a4a2fb9457b690e68d037"
        },
        {
            "question": "I bought the watch, ……………… it was expensive.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "however",
                "though",
                "despite"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cd4a2859e5b54c0b9e20a7d512e4e151"
        },
        {
            "question": "John didn’t come ……………….., everybody else did.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "though",
                "despite",
                "however"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "48479a664be147209c6849cf1f382781"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… the government refuses to admit it, it has failed to revive the economy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Although",
                "However",
                "Despite"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a456b1e9f1a64a5aabe41efb1505e92c"
        },
        {
            "question": "He failed ………………… his hard work.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "though",
                "in spite of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fc1cccdbb0e340bbb694bf0a5467ccf8"
        },
        {
            "question": "I didn’t like her rude behavior. ………………, I said nothing.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Despite",
                "Though",
                "However"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "920bfce529a24c9bba084c9ef4c3dcbe"
        }
    ]
}